Inventory of the Theodore Fred Abel papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- List of Individuals
  - #181: Lothar Thiel, birthdate: 1905, Nazi party number: 23806, number of pages: 9
  - #182: Ludwig Gabelmann, birthdate: 1885, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 6
  - #183: Richard Gumbert, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 3
  - #184: Karl Schlee, birthdate: 1902, Nazi party number: 20597, number of pages: 4
  - #185: Fritz Daemrich, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3
  - #186: Wilhelm Acht, birthdate: 1880, World War I service: 1915-1917, number of pages: 8
  - #187: Lisi Paupie, birthdate: 1891, Nazi party number: 1394006, number of pages: 22 (not typed)
  - #188: Fritz Fischer, birthdate: 1909, number of pages: 8 (typed)
  - #189: Wilhelm Höfler, birthdate: 1887, World War I service: 1916-1918, number of pages: 6
  - #190: Georg Fässig, birthdate: 1889, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 187012, number of pages: 30 (not typed)
  - #191: Walter Graulich, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 4 (typed)
  - #192: Paul Bierwirth, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: 1914-1915, Nazi party number: 90434, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #193: Frau E. Bierwirth, birthdate: 1896, Nazi party number: 90435, number of pages: 7
  - #194: H. Schönbohm, birthdate: 1882, World War I service: 1914-1915, Nazi party number: 5278, number of pages: 8 (typed)
  - #195: Maria Engelhardt, birthdate: 1898, Nazi party number: 98082, number of pages: 16
  - #196: Franz Fischer, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #197: Christoph Delp, birthdate: 1901, Nazi party number: 184402, number of pages: 4
  - #198: Willi Barth, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 5
  - #199: Hans Schonherr, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: from 1916, Nazi party number: 293778, number of pages: 8
  - #200: Fritz Hunn, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: from 1917, Fk., Nazi party number: 132388, number of pages: 3
  - #201: Johann Balser, birthdate: 1885, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #202: Johannes Jordan, birthdate: 1879, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 9
  - #203: Willi Schmidt, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 4
  - #204: missing
  - #205: Herbert H., birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 9 (not typed)
  - #206: Josef Jung, birthdate: 1911, number of pages: 9
  - #207: Helene Radtke, birthdate: 1896, Nazi party number: 218054, number of pages: 14 (typed)
  - #208: Philipp Ripper, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 6
  - #209: Karl Folning, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 5
  - #210: Schwarz, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: 1915-1920, number of pages: 6
  - #211: Reinhold Putz, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 10
  - #212: Maria von Belli, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 13
  - #213: Willy Wolf, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1917, Nazi party number: 37397, number of pages: 8
  - #214: Waldmann, birthdate: after 1900, number of pages: 9
  - #215: Peter Emig, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 5
  - #216: Kurt Liebelt, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 4
  - #217: Heinrich Muller, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 9 (not typed)
  - #218: Reinhold Wolf, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 6 (not typed)
  - #219: Kaun, birthdate: 1907, number of pages: 7
  - #220: Egon Rehmer, birthdate: 1907, number of pages: 4
  - #221: Marleimierstein ?, birthdate: circa 1895, World War I service: 1915-1918, number of pages: 11
  - #222: Aloys Folbach, birthdate: circa 1899, World War I service: circa from 1918, number of pages: 6
  - #223: Gumbert Heth, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 9 (not typed)
  - #224: Carl Haar, birthdate: 1904, Nazi party number: 231692, number of pages: 17 (typed)
  - #225: Harder, birthdate: before 1890, number of pages: 5
  - #226: Hermann Wischner, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, Nazi party number: 32466, number of pages: 9
  - #227: Ernst Glogau, birthdate: 1907, Nazi party number: 27255, number of pages: 9
  - #228: Otto Schulz, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 28 (not typed)
  - #229: Ernst Fischer, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1916-1919, number of pages: 5 (typed)
  - #230: Wilhelm Meyer, birthdate: 1883, World War I service: 1915-1918, Nazi party number: 297375, number of pages: 5
  - #231: Friedrich Schaub, birthdate: 1882, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #232: Karl Nüss, birthdate: 1905, number of pages: 11
  - #233: Bruno Thürling, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 6
  - #234: Alfred Schiffer, birthdate: 1890, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 7 (not typed)
  - #235: Hans Berthold, birthdate: 1871, World War I service: captured, Nazi party number: 180965, number of pages: 7 (typed)
  - #236: Wilhelm Braune, birthdate: 1871, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 14 (not typed)
  - #237: Kurt Roschewitz, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #238: Otto Dietrich, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 6
  - #239: Th. Schieben, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 10
  - #240: Walter Frantzen, birthdate: 1904, Nazi party number: 44246, number of pages: 5
  - #241: Hortmann, birthdate: 1895, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3
  - #242: SchüIter, birthdate: 1890, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 14
  - #243: August Kirwald, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 7
  - #244: R. Eiden, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 12
  - #245: Josef Schuiz, birthdate: after 1900, Nazi party number: 190729, number of pages: 7
  - #246: Wilhelm Rossbach, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 6
    Duplicates number 331.
  - #247: Murlebach, birthdate: 1881, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 9
  - #248: Adolf Reif, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, Nazi party number: 151224, number of pages: 6
  - #249: Horst Herzberg, birthdate: 1911, number of pages: 6
  - #250: Hermann Herx, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 18
  - #251: Hans Schumacher, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 28
  - #252: Reinhold Voss, birthdate: circa 1870, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 7
  - #253: Armin Franz, birthdate: 1879, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 80500, number of pages: 8
  - #254: Karl Zacher, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 5
  - #255: Wilhelm Gehmerts, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 12 (not typed)
  - #256: Hermann Muller, birthdate: 1876, World War I service: Landsturm (Militia), number of pages: 7 (typed)
  - #257: Alfred Raeschke, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 7
  - #258: G. Goretzki, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 16
  - #259: G. Hilger, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: Heimatlazar, number of pages: 8
  - #260: F. C. Prinz v. Schaumburg-Lippe, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 4
  - #261: Hollas Wilke, birthdate: after 1900, number of pages: 6
  - #262: Erich Femke, birthdate: 1885, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 19 (not typed)
  - #263: Max Hausmann, birthdate: 1889, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 11
  - #264: Hermann von Greve-Dierfeld, birthdate: 1869, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 12 (typed)
  - #265: Ernst Schmitt, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 8
  - #266: Walter Junglen, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 3
  - #267: Edmund Dienhardt, birthdate: after 1900, number of pages: 17
  - #268: Franz Merkelbach, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 6
  - #269: Carl John, birthdate: 1902, Nazi party number: 551156, number of pages: 3
  - #270: Georg Köhrbrück, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 88847, number of pages: 5
  - #271: Hans Teubner, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 8
  - #272: Walter Kählitz, birthdate: 1895, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 6
  - #273: Wilhelm Lembke, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #274: Richard Quack, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown-1918, number of pages: 5
  - #275: Max Schmidt, birthdate: 1895, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #276: Kurt Buschkowski, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: 1914-1918, Nazi party number: 924740, number of pages: 9
  - #277: Herbert Böhme, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 14
  - #278: Richard Weber, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 7
  - #279: Rillimke ?, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: yes, number of pages: 6
  - #280: Wilhelm Protz, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: 1915-1916, Nazi party number: 12907, number of pages: 10
  - #281: Wilhelm Nitschke, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: from 1916, Nazi party number: 59966, number of pages: 8
  - #282: Johann Scheer, birthdate: 1876, number of pages: 5
  - #283: Emil Setny, birthdate: 1888, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 5
  - #284: Walter Otto, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 9
  - #285: Alfred Klinghammer, birthdate: 1893, World War I service: 1914-1917, Nazi party number: 226605, number of pages: 8
  - #286: Karl Bennewitz, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 7
  - #287: Fritz Zabel, birthdate: 1878, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #288: Eduard Holema, birthdate: 1890, number of pages: 9
  - #289: Max Karsties, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: 1915-1918, number of pages: 16
  - #290: Bemhard Horstmann, birthdate: 1883, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 6
  - #291: Robert Reinecke, birthdate: 1879, World War I service: 1914-1918, Nazi party number: 3026, number of pages: 4
  - #292: Willy Reinke, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 9
  - #293: Bruno Stiffel, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 8
  - #294: Max Pollow, birthdate: 1908, Nazi party number: 411096, number of pages: 5
  - #295: Bruno Schulze, birthdate: 1889, Nazi party number: 531377, number of pages: 16
  - #296: Otto Hinz, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 11
  - #297: Frau H. Huhn, birthdate: before 1890, number of pages: 6
  - #298: Walther Schultz, birthdate: after 1900, Nazi party number: 141102, number of pages: 9 (not typed)
  - #299: Ferdinand Adler, birthdate: 1872, World War I service: 1915-1918, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #300: Georg Deutscher, birthdate: 1878, number of pages: 2
  - #301: Wilhelm Barnick, birthdate: 1877, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #302: Robert Eckert, birthdate: 1889, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4 (typed)
  - #303: Walter Henning, birthdate: 1882, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #304: Otto Klebow, birthdate: 1882, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 3
  - #305: Leokardia Kogalski, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 3
  - #306: Paul Kreuzmann, birthdate: 1904, Nazi party number: 25976, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #307: Stehen, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #308: Wilhelm Gebert, birthdate: 1880, number of pages: 4
  - #309: Karl Fleck, birthdate: 1890, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3
  - #310: Alfred Meissner, birthdate: 1880, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 6 (typed)
  - #311: Willi Luther, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 133090, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #312: Robert Fischer, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 4
  - #313: Walter Treue, birthdate: after 1900, Nazi party number: 335979, number of pages: 4
  - #314: unknown, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #315: Emil?, birthdate: 1880, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 2 (not typed)
  - #316: Wilhelm?, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 2
  - #317: Walter König, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #318: Karl Waldmann, birthdate: 1879, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 5 (not typed)
  - #319: Albert B., birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 3
  - #320: Julius Gebert, birthdate: 1883, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #321: Otto Albrecht, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3
  - #322: Otto Seiffarth, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2 (not typed)
  - #323: Johannes Schabert, birthdate: 1895, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 105874, number of pages: 8
  - #324: B. Huth, birthdate: 1876, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 4
  - #325: Fritz Czirnik, birthdate: 1879, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 10
  - #326: missing
  - #327: Paul Würschheim, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #328: Robert Wuttur, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 121983, number of pages: 2
  - #329: Paul Laczinier, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 5 (not typed)
  - #330: Knaut, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #331: Wilhelm Rossbach, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 6
    Duplicates number 246.
  - #332: Paul Lenz, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #333: Ernst Külm, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 6 (not typed)
  - #334: Johann Sch., birthdate: 1879, World War I service: 1915-1917, number of pages: 4 (typed)
  - #335: Wilhelm L., birthdate: 1878, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 151230, number of pages: 10 (not typed)
  - #336: missing
  - #337: missing
  - #338: missing
  - #339: missing
  - #340: Martin Hoffmann, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 6 (not typed)
  - #341: Hugo Bierbrauer, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, Nazi party number: 66520, number of pages: 2
  - #342: Mertes, birthdate: 1893, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 5
  - #343: Anton Idems, birthdate: 1900, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #344: Peter Wirschem, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 3
  - #345: Johann Klein, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #346: Johann Sturm, birthdate: 1903, number of pages: 2
  - #347: Eberhardt, birthdate: 1873, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 88119, number of pages: 1
  - #348: Arthur F., birthdate: 1889, World War I service: 1915-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #349: Oskar Klinkusch, birthdate: after 1900, Nazi party number: 163208, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #350: Josef Heimhauser, birthdate: 1873, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 11 (not typed)
  - #351: Frau ?, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 1 (typed)
  - #352: Paul Matter, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 2
  - #353: Marta Gruse, birthdate: 1889, number of pages: 10 (not typed)
  - #354: Arthur Klaffke, birthdate: 1901, Nazi party number: 278054, number of pages: 3
  - #355: Emil?, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 6
  - #356: Franz Wichmann, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 2
  - #357: Herbert Neumann, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 2
  - #358: Heinrich Remjul, birthdate: 1894, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 1
  - #359: Ernst Schröger, birthdate: 1911, number of pages: 1
  - #360: Ernst Lurkfett, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 2
  - #361: Erich Hinz, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 4
  - #362: Gunther Kelch, birthdate: 1890, World War I service: from 1918, number of pages: 2
  - #363: Erna Stoyke, birthdate: 1913, number of pages: 7 (typed)
  - #364: Bruno Krupp, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #365: Maria Wage, birthdate: 1867, number of pages: 3
  - #366: Gustav Bemeiker, birthdate: 1877, Nazi party number: 567295, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #367: M. Prinz, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #368: missing
  - #369: Wilhelm Bischoff, birthdate: 1893, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #370: Hermann ?, birthdate: 1907, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #371: Otto Schneider, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 2
  - #372: Max Lenz, birthdate: 1902, Nazi party number: 357633, number of pages: 1
  - #373: Wiesch ?, birthdate: 1900, World War I service: October 1918, number of pages: 2
  - #374: Wilhelm Gang, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 26
  - #375: Ewald Bahr, birthdate: 1910, Nazi party number: 127453, number of pages: 5 (typed)
  - #376: Rudolf Heidke, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #377: keine Ab.! [Mitteilungsblatt der Sektion Mommsen der NSDAP], number of pages: 10 (typed)
  - #378: Paul Barz, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #379: H. L. v. Berswordt-wallrabe, birthdate: 1912, Nazi party number: 320417, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #380: Reindling, birthdate: 1885, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 6 (not typed)
  - #381: Bohli, birthdate: 1884, World War I service: Gamison, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #382: Euler, birthdate: 1910, number of pages: 2
  - #383: Georg Kreidel, birthdate: 1873, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #384: Karl G. Müller, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 5 (not typed)
  - #385: Ferdinand Zehnder, birthdate: 1906, Nazi party number: 17369, number of pages: 3
  - #386: Wilhelm Schneider, birthdate: 1886, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 7
  - #387: Bruno Seidel, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 276539, number of pages: 4
  - #388: Zimmer, birthdate: 1883, number of pages: 2
  - #389: William Berlinghof, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #390: Maria Zurlinden, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #391: Martin Gorn, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 5
  - #392: Karl F. Nau, birthdate: 1912, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #393: Paul Heilmann, birthdate: 1894, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #394: Karl H. Geitz, birthdate: 1903, number of pages: 2
  - #395: Wilhelm Heim, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 2
  - #396: Ludwig Weber, birthdate: 1890, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #397: Kurt Schertler, birthdate: 1913, number of pages: 2
  - #398: Wilhelm Gorf, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #399: Philipp Schneider, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 1 (typed)
  - #400: Raimund Mayer, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1915, number of pages: 2
  - #401: H. Schieferstein, birthdate: before 1890, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2
  - #402: August Arnold, birthdate: 1907, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #403: Wilhelm Fischer, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 5
  - #404: Hans Home, birthdate: 1895, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 5
  - #405: Kurt Constantz, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 2
  - #406: Stahl, birthdate: 1911, number of pages: 4 (typed)
  - #407: Wilhelm Henkel, birthdate: 1907, number of pages: 2
  - #408: Fritz Keppner, birthdate: 1901, number of pages: 2
  - #409: Hermann Jung, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 1
  - #410: A. Anschütz, birthdate: 1903, number of pages: 2
  - #411: Alois Rein, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 2
  - #412: Ludwig Kalkbrenner, birthdate: 1903, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #413: Willi Miesel, birthdate: unknown, Nazi party number: 23808, number of pages: 3
  - #414: August Nunold, birthdate: 1900, World War I service: from July 1918, number of pages: 3
  - #415: Erich Klein, birthdate: 1905, number of pages: 4 (typed)
  - #416: Paul Moschel, birthdate: 1903, Nazi party number: 28454, number of pages: 4
  - #417: Ludwig Schneider, birthdate: 1887, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #418: Friedrich Schurtz, birthdate: 1869, World War I service: unknown, Nazi party number: 8272, number of pages: 2 (not typed)
  - #419: Heinrich Mayer, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 5 (typed)
  - #420: Johann Eckel, birthdate: 1873, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 2 (not typed)
  - #421: Ludwig Butz, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: from 1916, number of pages: 3
  - #422: Willibald Kranz, birthdate: 1904, Nazi party number: 2930, number of pages: 3
  - #423: Karl Henss, birthdate: 1901, Nazi party number: 29545, number of pages: 6
  - #424: Kurt Hom, birthdate: 1908, Nazi party number: SS 11177, number of pages: 2
  - #425: Fritz Gröschei, birthdate: 1900, World War I service: from 1918, Nazi party number: 288677, number of pages: 6
  - #426: A. Knell, birthdate: 1902, World War I service: Freikorps, number of pages: 4
  - #427: August Fischer, birthdate: 1905, number of pages: 5
  - #428: J. Arnold Reiss, birthdate: 1891, number of pages: 5
  - #429: Theo Tisch, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 4
  - #430: Karl Schumacher, birthdate: circa 1890, World War I service: 1914-1917, Nazi party number: 76275, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #431: Ernst Kreiselmaier, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 2
  - #432: Oberfrank, birthdate: unknown, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 1
  - #433: Philipp Baumann, birthdate: 1903, number of pages: 2
  - #434: Christian Gautsche, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 2
  - #435: Robert Friedrich, birthdate: 1882, World War I service: 1914-1917, number of pages: 5
  - #436: Willi Scharf, birthdate: 1904, number of pages: 3
  - #437: Georg Winkler, birthdate: 1908, number of pages: 1
  - #438: Franz Bentz, birthdate: 1897, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 2
  - #439: Erich Kiefer, birthdate: 1906, Nazi party number: 20585, number of pages: 2
  - #440: Karl Münch, birthdate: 1898, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 2
  - #441: August Acker, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 1
  - #442: Friedrich Luther, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 2
  - #443: Eugen Huber, birthdate: 1902, number of pages: 2
  - #444: Jakob Bösch, birthdate: 1891, World War I service: unknown, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #445: Ernst Erbelding, birthdate: 1892, World War I service: 1914-1920, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #446: Karl Dreher, birthdate: 1896, World War I service: 1915-1917, number of pages: 1
  - #447: Fritz Leixner, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: n.kv. [nicht kriegsverwendungsfähig, not fit to serve in war], number of pages: 1
  - #448: Heinrich Pickl, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 3 (not typed)
  - #449: Ernst Botz, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 1
  - #450: Otto Breugel, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 1
  - #451: Karl Wuttke, birthdate: 1907, Nazi party number: 69800, number of pages: 2 (typed)
  - #452: Jakob Ackermann, birthdate: 1894, World War I service: 1914-1918, number of pages: 3
  - #453: Susi Jost, birthdate: unknown, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #454: Mossel, birthdate: 1876, World War I service: 1915-1918, number of pages: 3 (typed)
  - #455: Ludwig Becker, birthdate: 1899, World War I service: from 1917, number of pages: 4 (not typed)
  - #456: Maria Wiebe, birthdate: 1871, number of pages: 11
  - #457: Marianne Heimer, birthdate: 1906, number of pages: 14
  - #458: Helmut Mateske, birthdate: 1898, Nazi party number: 319369, number of pages: 6